# Jordy Bukonda Tshibangu

Junior fullstack engineer

### **Details**

#### Address

13 Bloemendal road Mowbray Cape Town, 7700 South Africa

#### Phone

0682866579

#### **Email**

jordytshibss@gmai.com

#### Date / Place of birth

1 August 1997 Kinshasa, Republic Democratic of Congo

#### Nationality

Congolese

### Skills

#### Adaptability

Ability to Work in a Team

. . . .

Communication

 $\bullet$ 

Good team worker

 $\bullet$ 

**Decision Making Skills** 

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$ 

Eager to learn

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$ 

**Problem Solving Skills** 

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$ 

Fast Leaner

• • • • •

Detail-oriented

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$ 

Googling

### **Profile**

Passionate software engineering graduate from the Cape Peninsula University of Technology with 2 years and 6 months experience in software development. Creative full-stack engineer who prices on details and achievement. Seeking to use acquired skills in JavaScript, PHP and C#, and to learn about multiple tech.

# **Employment History**

#### **Programming Tutor, CPUT**

Aug 2018 - Aug 2019

Cape Town, South Africa

I tutored students who had difficulties in mathematics and programming. My job was to help them understanding the basics of C++ which we used to build embedded system with Arduino.

### Intern software developer, Nona digital

Feb 2019 — Feb 2020

Cape Town, South Africa

I worked at Nona digital as an intern software developer.

I started at a QA position where I wrote the end to end test for the site and was later on the front-end side of projects, where I restyled some important part of the website I was working on.

And finally, I tested the entire project using the Cypress library.

I worked as a front-end developer in projects such as

www.gostackr.com, www.go2africa.com

#### Junior Software developer, Codeswop

Dec 2020 – Jun 2021

Cape Town, South Africa

I worked at Codeswop as a front-end developer.

During my spell at Codeswop, the MeditPet project I worked on had to go through some refactoring, and using my knowledge of React and Redux, we changed some functionality and styling across the site.

#### Frontend Software developer, Fireworkx

Sep 2021 − Present 

Cape Town, South Africa

- Implemented and updated application modules under the direction of Senior Software Developers.
- Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.
- Built and implemented different type of innovative software.

## Languages

French

• • • •

English

. . . . .

Lingala

. . . . .

### Links

GitHub

I have worked and am working on different projects, providing my frontend engineering skills, applying javascript, HTML and CSS in projects such as:

- Santamre (www-acc.santamre.com)
- Santam.co.za
- MandG (Prudential)
- AndyCab

### Education

### Mater Dei, Matric

I majored in Biology and chemistry, combined with mathematics, physics and communication skills

#### UNIKIN, Preparatory Polytechnic

I started my electrical engineering path in Polytechnic at the University of Kinshasa where I acquired mathematical, and physical skills

I learned how to have a logical thinking and a problem solving mentality, how to approach complex mathematical and physical problems

### Cape Peninsula University of Technology, National Diploma

My electrical engineering studies at CPUT helped me to clearly understand the concept of electrical engineering and better embrace the computer system world, including Network, IT essential and Programming.

#### LinkedIn Learning, Udemy, W3School and Edx

Aug 2019 − Present 

Online

As an intern at Nona digital, I studied basics and advanced topics about programming languages such as

- JavaScript (ReactJS, VueJS Express NodeJS, GraphQL, Socket.io)
- PHP (OOP-PHP, Laravel)
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- SCSS, Sass
- Asp.net core

# **Computer Skills**

#### Frontend stack

- HTML, CSS (SCSS, Sass, Tailwind CSS)
- Bootstrap, JQuery, MATERIAL UI

- JavaScript (DOM manipulation)
- React.JS ( React Hooks, Context, Redux, Styled Component, React-bootstrap )
- Next JS (Server Side Rendering)
- Vue.JS (Routing, Pinia state management, Vue-router, Composition API)
- NuxtJS (Server Side Rendering)
- Third-party:

Git, GitHub, NPM, yarn, GitLab, Slack, JIRA, Agile, Composer, ...

#### Backend stack

- Node.Js: (ExpressJs, Socket.io, GraphQL)
- GraphQL: (GraphQL-yoga, Prisma ORM, GraphQL-express)
- PHP: ( Laravel, WordPress)
- Java: (Basics of Java Concepts, OOP)
- C# .net : (Basic concepts, OOP, currently learning ASP.net Core)
- Meteor Js: ( A JavaScript full-stack framework)

#### Database (Oracle, MySQL, MongoDB, Microsoft Access)

I have worked with Oracle and MySQL during my university years and beyond those years, I have enhanced the skills I acquired at university from my studies

I learned MongoDB and built couple of projects using it.

### Agile Methodology

During my internship I learned and applied the Agile methodology while working in projects.

Using Jira board, standups, Slack, and Sprint

### References

#### Richard Miles

Team Lead and Senior Developer at Atheneum Partners

richlloydmiles@gmail.com

#### **Quinton Arendse**

Project Manager Fireworkx

+27 73 388 6045

### Courses

# Internships